wdrv.it 2014-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Wiredrive

_Document updated October 2013_

We created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the protection of your privacy. We recognize that personal and company information that may be entered in this site or disclosed to our staff may be of a confidential or sensitive nature. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website and the quality of our services. It is not shared with or sold to any other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you have requested, but only when we have your permission.

The following sections cover the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Wiredrive anytime you interact with Wiredrive, such as when you visit our website, or when you call or email our sales or support teams.

## Collecting information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

## Tracking information

We use cookies to store and track information about you throughout the session at our web site. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your hard drive.

Generally, we use cookies to serve you better and to save time. You are given a cookie that will recognize you as a repeat registered user and store your user name for the login. This cookie maintains your identity while you log in and allows you to access your account and stored documents. This cookie expires after you log out. There is also a session cookie with a time-out function that disappears once you logout of the website. The cookie also expires for security purposes after a certain amount of time so that your program will not continually run without user activity.

We collect IP addresses for system administration and to report the aggregate information for our personal use. Your IP address is also used to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our web site.

## Security guarantee

Your personal contact information and uploaded media are secure with Wiredrive. The uploaded media are visible only to the specific parties you invite to use your account. They are not visible to any other users or non-users of this web site. We use industry standard methods to protect your personal and media information from unauthorized access. We are not responsible, however, if a third party accesses your information by breaching our security measures.

## Communications and publicity

Per our company policy, we do not provide a list of users, user addresses, user email addresses or other such user information to third parties for commercial purposes. From time to time, however, Wiredrive may send you email, direct mail, faxes or contact you by other means to make you aware of promotional offerings, service upgrades and updates, partner/alliance announcements and other important information. Additionally, Wiredrive may occasionally reference your company name in customer lists or press releases issued regarding the licensing of the software and/or usage of our site.

## Contacting Wiredrive

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you may contact [Wiredrive support](mailto:support@wiredrive.com).

## Changes to this privacy statement

Any changes to this policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Please check back periodically if you have any concerns about changes made to our privacy policy.
